sweetwater.com 2015-06-23

# Privacy Policy | Help Center | Sweetwater.com

### Our Commitment to Privacy

We are glad that you have chosen to shop at Sweetwater.com. We are committed to protecting your privacy online. This page explains how we collect, use and protect the information that you provide to us. We respect your privacy and intend to give you as much control as possible over your personal information. 

### What Information Do We Collect?

  * **Information That You Provide Us**

We accept and store any information that you submit on Sweetwater.com or by any other means. For example, you may provide personal information when you place an order, enter a giveaway, request a publication, or contact us. This information may include name, address, phone numbers, email address, credit card and payment information, and other personal information.

  * **Telephone Calls with Sweetwater**

We constantly review our own performance to ensure that we're providing exceptional service and support. Some phone calls are recorded or monitored for training purposes.

  * **Web Site Use Information**

We collect and analyze technical information about how customers interact with Sweetwater.com including, but not limited to, IP addresses, browser types, operating systems, pages viewed, links, dates and times, and other information.

  * **Cookies**

Like many websites, we utilize a standard technology called "cookies" to differentiate you from other shoppers and to store and retrieve information about your interaction with the website, like the items in your shopping cart or wishlist for example.

  * **Email Information and Contact Forms**

We may collect, store, and use any information that you submit via email or any of the forms on our website. We may also collect information about email communications such as confirming that an email was opened or which links were clicked.

### How We Use Collected Information

We use collected information for the purpose of administering our business activities such as completing and tracking orders, customer service, communicating with customers, administering giveaways and other promotions, customizing the shopping experience, troubleshooting, improving the website design and functionality, and other business uses. From time to time, we may send you promotional messages by mail or email. You will always have the option to opt out of such communications (see below).

We do not intentionally share your information with third parties except as required by law or to facilitate business operations (such as shipping partners and payment processors).

### How We Protect Your Information

In order to protect your information, we have put in place appropriate electronic, physical, and procedural safeguards. We utilize standard encryption/security technology to protect data transfer and our information systems are treated with the highest regard for security. In addition, we limit access to customer information to only authorized personnel.

### How You Can Review or Correct Your Information

To review or correct your personal information, or to change your communication preferences, please call us at 800-222-4700. Your Sales Engineer will be glad to help. You may choose to stop receiving promotional communications at any time. If you have subscribed to any of our email newsletters, you may unsubscribe anytime.

### Links to Other Websites

Sweetwater is not responsible for the content or practices employed by other websites that are linked to from Sweetwater.com. When you use a link to go from Sweetwater.com to another website, our privacy policy is no longer in effect.

### Your Consent

By using our website you consent to our collection and use of your personal information as described in this Policy. If we change our policies and procedures, we will post those changes on our website to keep you aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we may disclose it.

This policy was last updated on January 16, 2006. If you have any questions or concerns about this privacy policy, please call us at 800-222-4700 or contact us. 

#### Can We Help?

Sweetwater is committed to providing the best shopping experience in the industry. You can find information regarding Sweetwater.com policies and services to the left.

##### Questions? Call us toll-free **(800) 222-4700**
